IZABELA KRUPINSKA

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PERSONAL DETAILS

ADDRESS

Wolverhampton United Kingdom

PHONE

+447868197008

EMAIL

izabkru88@gmail.com

WEBSITES & SOCIAL LINKS

Linkedin

<u>GitHub</u>

Portfolio Website

CORE SKILLS

Python

Django

Django REST API

JavaScript

React

HTML & CSS

Automated Testing

GitHub

PostgreSQL

HOBBIES

Gaming, Traveling, Cooking

PERSONAL PROFILE

Motivated Junior Software Developer, recently graduated with a Higher National Diploma in Software Development with a strong focus on Python and Django.

Have 1+ non-commercial experience working with Python, Django, PostgreSQL, JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS and unit testing.

A detail-oriented, organized and hard-working employee, strongly focused on the quality of the code. Work at a fast pace to meet tight deadlines. An enthusiastic team player ready to contribute to the company's success.

EDUCATION

Higher National Diploma, Code Institute

Aug 2021 — Aug 2022

- The Diploma in Full Stack Software Development (E-commerce Applications)
 has been credit-rated by the University of the West of Scotland at level 8 on
 the Scottish Credit & Qualifications Framework with 60 SCQF credit points.
- This, in turn, equates to level 5 on the European Qualification Framework (EQF).

PROJECTS

* NORAH'S CERAMICS

May 2022 — Jul 2022

Norah's Ceramics - an online shop with handmade ceramic and glass products and also zero-waste accessories for the kitchen and bathroom. This e-commerce business is B2C oriented.

- Full stack e-commerce website involving CRUD operations, real payment infrastructure and authentication.
- · Created with an Agile methodology to plan and design the site.
- Build with: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Stripe, Python, and Django as a framework.
- · GitHub link

* THE WALKERS

Jan 2022 — Apr 2022

The Walkers - a platform for people who are both: looking for dog carers and people providing such services in the United Kingdom.

- Full-Stack platform involving CRUD operations, based on business logic, used to control a centrally-owned dataset.
- Contain an authentication mechanism, and provide role-based access to site data.

- · Created with an Agile methodology to plan and design the site.
- Build with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Python, and Django as a framework.
- · GitHub link

* BRAINSTORM QUIZ

Nov 2021 — Dec 2021

Brainstorm Quiz is a quiz game. The goal of the Brainstorm Quiz is to become the Brainstorm Champion. To achieve this, the player must answer all questions.

- A command-line application designed to be used from a text interface(such as a shell).
- · Build with Python.
- · GitHub link

* CUP&CAKE

Sep 2021 — Nov 2021

CUP&CAKE website is a landing page for a pastry shop that bakes cupcakes and sends them directly to customers' homes.

- The front-end site responds to users' actions by enabling them to engage with the data actively and change the way information is displayed to meet their preferred goals.
- · Builds with HTML and CSS, and JavaScript.
- · GitHub link

* DOG INN

Aug 2021 — Aug 2021

Dog Inn website is a landing page for all dog owners looking for a place where they can leave their dogs during their absence.

- The static front-end site builds with HTML and CSS, and JavaScript.
- GitHub link

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Warehouse Team Member, Antalis

Coalville, United Kingdom

Aug 2015 — Aug 2020

Key responsibilities:

- · Followed all instructions and safety procedures during work.
- · Collaborated with teams to meet daily shipping schedules.
- Assisting with the unloading and loading of vehicles and the checking in of stock.
- Collecting items throughout the warehouse, preparing and completing warehouse orders for delivery or pickup according to a schedule.

Pub Manager, Piccadilly Pub

Olsztyn, Poland

Jan 2014 — Nov 2014

Key responsibilities:

- · Recruiting, training and supervising staff.
- · Managing budgets.
- · Maintaining statistical and financial records.

- · Planning and taking part in promotional events.
- · Analyzed loss and profit reports.
- Encouraging open communication and a strong team spirit among employees.

Executive Sales Representative, Concord Sp z o o

Olsztynek, Poland

Feb 2012 — Dec 2012

Key responsibilities:

- · Negotiating contracts with prospective clients.
- Helping determine pricing schedules for quotes, promotions, and negotiations.
- · Preparing weekly and monthly reports.
- Visiting clients and potential clients to evaluate needs or promote products and services.
- · Maintaining client records.

Key achievements:

· Multiple exceeding the agreed monthly sales targets.

COURSES

Build a Backend REST API with Python & Django - Advanced, Udemy

Sep 2022 — Present

Build a Backend REST API with Python & Django - Beginner, Udemy

Sep 2022 — Sep 2022

Front End Developer, Udacity

Apr 2020 — Jul 2020

Modern HTML & CSS From The Beginning, Udemy

Sep 2019 — Dec 2019